This project has been really hard for me.
I'm working on two different projects right now
and it's just too much.
I've also been feeling disconnected from this team,
and I don't have the full picture
of what we're trying to accomplish.
Honestly, Alisha, I think we need to step back as a team
and align on priorities and deadlines.
I could use some clarity, especially when it comes
to dependencies across work streams.
Also, confidentially, I'm feeling a ton of pressure
coming out of my last performance review.
So I didn't want to raise a flag that this is just too much work,
but honestly, it feels like I'm trying to do two full-time jobs
and failing at both.
And I think each of my team leaders believes
that their project is my primary assignment.
It just feels like I'm letting everyone down.